I sell TikTok shop agency services to econ brands.
We do two and a half million in revenue.
I'd like to be at twelve.
What's stopping me is women in the red dress.
Who's with me today? Yeah, she's there.
She is stunning supplements brand growing like crazy on TikTok shop.
Obviously, the agency kind of services, the growth, which is great.
I can't do both.
I know what you're going to say, but it's fucking fifty fifty.
I don't know which way to go.
I'll tell you this. There's no right answer.
It's going to be what you want to do.
If I were you, I would take my existing very large infrastructure
on the agency side, cut all my clients and then take all that marketing
horsepower and put it towards and then own a big ass brand.
What stops you from doing that?
I love the agency side. OK.
Also, I do see a huge opportunity in the info product model with it
because a lot of people would buy it.
Well, you said you want to get to 12 million. Mm hmm.
Either this could get to 12 million.
Mm hmm. Coaching business gets to 12 million.
You can sell socks and get to 12 million.
What do you want to do?
Would you prefer to be an agency owner? Yeah, I would. OK.
Your existing agency model wouldn't get you there.
You'd have to serve as higher end customers.
And I think rather than trying to invest in the brands, just do a revenue share.
And then the info product that a lot of people might be interested in,
we could just sell that and then.
Yeah, or you could just not sell it.
You could just you could just live your life
and just serve as the high end customers and make more money.
Like, this is a discipline thing.
There will always be more opportunities than you can possibly do.
It's just the nature of life, life short.
And you'd like and the more skilled you are,
the more amazing opportunities you have to say no to.
It's like, you know what? I also think in like all these small guys,
they also need a little software.
And we could I could put this to it's like to stop.
Like, why not sell newspapers?
Right. Want some orange juice? They drink orange juice.
I mean, you know, like, like, what are we doing? Right.
If you just do one thing really well for the rest of your life,
it'll get really big.
But if you do two things for the rest of your life,
you won't either do either of them really well and neither will get big.
You have to just learn to say no.